A Guide to the Stacy May papers FA442
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subgroup 2, 1932-1971; 2; 11.99 Cubic Feet 25 legal-sized document boxes, 1 half-legal-sized document box
  - "The Production Statement, United States War Program July 1, 1940-August 31, 1945" - Civilian Production Administration, 1947 May (Box 85, Folder 525)
  - "United States Munitions Handbook" - Civilian Production Administration, 1947 May (Box 85, Folder 526)
  - "Official Munitions Production of the United States by Months, July 1, 1940-August 31, 1945" - Civilian Production Administration, 1947 May (Box 86, Folder 527)
  - Advisory Committee on Tropical Medicine - National Academy of Sciences, 1960-1964 (Box 86, Folder 528)
  - National Planning Association - Committee on Overseas Development, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 529)
  - Reed College - Portland, Oregon, 1932-1934, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 530)
  - Stock Market Trends and U. S. Markets, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 531)
  - Advisory Committee on Private Enterprise in Foreign Aid, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 532)
  - "Industrial Mobilization for War: History of the War Production Board and Predecessor Agencies, 1940 to 1945" - Source Book of Historical Statistics, 1946-1947 (Box 87, Folder 533)
  - National Planning Association - Advisory Committee on Latin American Economic Relations, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 534)
  - National Planning Association - America's New Opportunities in World Trade, 1944-1945 (Box 87, Folder 535)
  - National Planning Association - Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 87, Folder 536)
  - National Planning Association - General, 1952-1965 (Box 87, Folder 537, Box 88, Folder 538)
    Folder 537 - 1952-1964; Folder 538 - 1965
  - National Planning Association - General Reports, 1944 October-1946 June (Box 88, Folder 539-541, Box 89, Folder 542)
    Folder 539-540 - 1944 October-1945 June; Folder 541 - 1945 July-December; Folder 542 - 1946 January-June
  - National Planning Association - Interamerican Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 89, Folder 543)
  - National Planning Association - International Committee, 1944-1946 (Box 89, Folder 544-546, Box 90, Folder 547)
    Folder 544 - 1944 February-1945 December; Folder 545 - 1946 January-May; Folder 546 - 1946 June-December; Folder 547 - Bretton Woods, 1945
  - National Planning Association - Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 90, Folder 548-549)
  - National Planning Association - Nathan Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 90, Folder 550)
  - National Planning Association - Productive Uses of Nuclear Energy, 1954-1958 (Box 91, Folder 551)
  - National Planning Association - Special Project Committee on the Economics of Competitive Coexistence, 1956-1961 (Box 91, Folder 552)
  - National Planning Association - Wages and Productivity Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 91, Folder 553)
  - Advisory Council to Columbia University's School of International Affairs, 1961-1964 (Box 91, Folder 554)
  - American Economic Association - Source Book Economic Statistics, 1945-1946 (Box 91, Folder 555)
  - The American Foundation for Tropical Medicine, Inc., 1965 (Box 91, Folder 556)
  - American International Association (AIA), 1963-1965 (Box 92, Folder 557)
  - Business Advisory Council, 1945-1946 (Box 92, Folder 558-561)
    Folder 558 - 1944 January-May; Folder 559 - 1945 May-December; Folder 560 - 1946; Folder 561 - Statistics Committee - 1945
  - Civilian Production Administration - Members of the Advisory Council to the War Production Board Historian, 1946 (Box 92, Folder 562)
  - Conference of Business Economists, 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 563)
  - Conference on Development and Cooperation in the South Asia Pacific Region, February 24-29, 1964, 1960, 1963, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 564)
    Conference sponsored by the Council on World Tensions and the University of Malaya
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1944, 1946, 1948, 1953-1964 (Box 93, Folder 565-568, Box 94, Folder 569-572)
    Folder 565 - 1944; Folder 566 - 1946; Folder 567 - Membership Committee - 1953-1958, 1960, 1962; Folders 568-569 - General - 1948, 1953, 1955-1964; Folder 570 - Economic Integration in Latin America - 1960 July-1961 March; Folder 571 - Economic Integration in Latin America - 1961 April-1962 January; Folder 572 - Alliance for Progress Discussion Group - 1963-1964
  - Escuela Agricola Panamericana, Inc., 1948, 1960, 1962-1964, 1966-1970 (Box 94, Folder 573, Box 95, Folder 574-578, Box 96, Folder 579)
    Folder 573 - Marts and Lundy, Inc. - 1960; Folder 574 - Zamorano School - 1962; Folder 575 - Zamorano School - 1963; Folder 576 - Zamorano School - 1964; Folder 577 - 1948, 1966-1967; Folder 578 - 1968; Folder 579 - 1969-1970
  - Insurance Holding Companies, 1967-1969 (Box 96, Folder 580-582)
    Folder 580 - 1967; Folder 581 - 1968; Folder 582 - 1969
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Swedish Interamerican Co., Inc., 1949 (Box 97, Folder 583)
  - International Cooperation Year, 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 584)
  - Jobs, 1934-1940 (Box 97, Folder 585)
  - Latin America Science Board - Ninth Meeting, September 1965 (Box 97, Folder 586)
  - "Most of the Free World is Underdeveloped", 1949 (Box 97, Folder 587)
  - National Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 12th Anniversary Meeting, May 27-28, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 588)
  - National Institute of Development and Administration (NIDA), Thailand, 1966-1967, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 589)
  - National Planning Association, Center for Economic Projections - Draft - "Economic Base Study - State of New York", 1965 March-April (Box 97, Folder 590)
  - National Planning Association - "Central America: Regional Integration and Economic Development", 1967 (Box 98, Folder 591)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Position Papers on Economic Issues, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 592)
  - Notebooks (Box 98, Folder 593)
  - "A Report to Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller Suggesting a New Approach to Urban Design and a 'New City' of Neighborhood Centers for Lower Manhattan", 1964 (Box 98, Folder 594)
    Prepared by Harrison and Abramovitz - Architects
  - Rockefeller Center Luncheon Club, 1948-1949, 1951-1953, 1956-1964 (Box 98, Folder 595)
  - SM to File - Miscellaneous, 1935, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 596)
  - State of New York, Executive Department, 1965, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 597)
  - U. S. Council's Committee on Raw Materials, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 598)
  - "U. S. Foreign Trade Policy", 1963 November (Box 99, Folder 599)
  - U. S.-Peru Workshop on Science, Technology and Development - Background Information, 1966 April (Box 99, Folder 600)
  - Unfoldered Material, 1938, 1941, 1953, 1955-1956, 1959-1962, 1965-1966, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 601)
  - War Production Board - Historical Staff, 1945-1946 (Box 99, Folder 602)
  - Waring Group, 1945 (Box 99, Folder 603)
  - World Trade Foundation, 1946 (Box 99, Folder 604)
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 605)
    "Culture and Technical Assistance", a speech by Joseph L. Sutton, September 1959; "Opportunities for the Less Developed Nations in the Mineral Resource Field", by William F. Butler and George E. Kruger; Conference on Transportation Research, National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, Publication 840, August 1960
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 100, Folder 606)
    "Measures of State and Local Fiscal Capacity and Tax Effort", The Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, October 1962; "A Ten Year Report: 1954-1963", The Falk Project for Economic Research in Israel; "Economic Analysis of the Budget", by Emerson P. Schmidt, Chamber of Commerce of the United States; "The Scope and Financing of Urban Renewal and Development", a Statement by the NPA Business Committee and a Report by Peter Wagner, April 1963; "Looking Ahead", National Planning Association, Vol. 11, No. 9, December 1963; European Monetary Agreement", Fifth Annual Report of the Board of Management, 1963
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1964 January-October (Box 100, Folder 607)
    Connecticut Interregional Planning Program, Program Design, January 1964; "Business Conditions", a review by the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago, March 1964; "Changing Challenge of Communism: Some Implications for United States Policy", by Philip E. Mosely, May 1964; "Economic and Political Trends in Latin America", Proceedings of the Academy of Political Science May 1964; "Aids to Business (Overseas Investment)", United States Government Memorandum, July 1964; "Monetary Responsibilites in the 1960's", by Roy L. Reierson, July 1964; "The Euro-Dollar Market", Economics Department, Bankers Trust Company, July 1964; "The Soviet Union, Arms Control, and Disarmament: A Study of Soviet Attitudes", School of International Affairs, Columbia University, October 1964
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 608)
    The Foreign Assistance Program, Annual Report to the Congress, Fiscal Year 1964; Resources for the Future, Inc., Annual Report 1964; "Voluntary Associations", by Immanuel Wallerstein, reprinted from "Political Parties and National Integration in Tropical Africa", 1964; "European Sources for Tropical African History", by Graham Irwin; Purchasing Power Map of Europe; American and Foreign Power Company, Inc., Annual Report 1964; International Basic Economy Corporation, Annual Report 1964; "South Asia Pacific Crisis", edited by Margaret Grant
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 609)
    "The United States and the United Arab Republic: A Crisis in Confidence", by John S. Badeau, January 1965; State of New York Annual Budget Message, 1965-66, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Governor, T. N Hurd, Director of the Budget, January 1965; "The Economic Challenge of Communism", June 1, 1960, accompanying letter from John H. Hoagland, February 26, 1965; Business and Financial Trends, Second Quarter 1965, The Chase Manhattan Bank; "The Dollar Cost of our National Goals", by Leonard A. Lecht, National Planning Association, May 1965; "Noticias" Weekly Digest of Hemisphere Reports, National Foreign Trade Council, Inc., Volume XXI, Number 20, May 19, 1965
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 101, Folder 610)
    One Hundred and Eighth Annual Report of the Superintendent of Insurance to the New York Legislature Covering the Calendar Year 1966; One Hundred and Ninth Annual Report of the Superintendent of Insurance to the New York Legislature Covering the Calendar Year 1967; "Ritural and Reality in Insurance Regulation", Remarks of Richard E. Stewart, October 1968, and accompanying letter and photograph from Richard Stewart, October 30, 1968; "Republican Convention Scorecard - 667 Votes Needed for Nomination", The Boston Globe, August 7, 1068